// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Data science is the process of diverse set of data through?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Organizing data",
      "Processing data",
      "Analysing data",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The modern conception of data science as an independent discipline is sometimes attributed to?",
    answer: "William S.",
    options: [
      "William S.",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Arthur Samuel",
      "Satoshi Nakamoto"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a part of data science process?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Data Engineering",
      "Advanced Computing",
      "Domain expertise",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which among the following is the top most important thing in data science? How is raw data processed ?",
    answer: "Question",
    options: [
      "Answer",
      "Question",
      "Data",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following language is not used in data science ?",
    answer: "Html",
    options: [
      "Html",
      "C++",
      "Python",
      "C"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which approach should be used if you canâ€™t fix the variable?",
    answer: "Randomize it",
    options: [
      "Non stratify it",
      "Generalize it",
      "Randomize it",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "_________ is a good way of performing experiments in data science?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Have Replication",
      "Generalize to the problem",
      "Measure variability",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The kernels used in SVM are ___________?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Gaussian Kernel",
      "Polynomial Kernel",
      "Sigmoid Kernel",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Some of the important libraries of Python that are used in Data Science are _________.?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "Pandas",
      "Numpy",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which format do we need to upload the student data on Khelo India School Portal?",
    answer: "Excel Sheet",
    options: [
      "Word Document",
      "PDF",
      "PPT",
      "Excel Sheet"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];